Guide to the Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
- Drawings, 1924-2004
  - Capitol Broadcasting Company: WRAL TV (Tube 794)
    Landscape Development
  - Carmichael (Georgia and Fred) residence, 1974 (Tube 143)
    Preliminary landscape plan, elevations, floor plans, topographic survey
    Willis James B. Jr.; Bell Design Group; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Carmichael (Georgia and Fred) residence, 1976-1978 (Tube 831)
    Site Plans, Staking, Planting, Grading, Landscape Development, Details
  - Carnes Corporation: East Plant, 1965 (Tube 738)
    Leif Valand & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Sanford (N.C.)
  - Carolina Power and Light Company (1 of 2), 1967 (Tube 164)
  - Carolina Power and Light Company (2 of 2), 1967 (Tube 167)
    Site development plan of proposed sub-station
  - Carolina Power and Light Company: Proposed office and service facility, 1986 (Tube 571)
    Site development plan
    Bell Design Group; Garner (N.C.)
  - Carolina Power and Light Company: Proposed substation, 1967 (Tube 718)
    Site Development Plan of Proposed Substation, Schematic Plan, Schematic Grading, Planting Plan and Elevation
  - Carolinian Hotel, 1959-1963 (Tube 739)
    Construction Plan and Details, Plan and Details
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Nags Head (N.C.)
  - Carolinian Hotel: Construction plan and details, general landscape plan, 1959 (Tube 30)
    Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Nags Head (N.C.)
  - Carolinian Motor Hotel: Plans and details, 1963 (Tube 30)
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Nags Head (N.C.)
  - Carrboro Community Center, 1980 (Tube 857)
    Details: Comfort Station, Site Plan, Sanitary Sewer Force Main, Pump Station Details, Bath House Plan, Bath House Details, Bath House Foundation/Framing Plan
    Bell Design Group; John R. McAdams Company, Inc.; Kolodij Roman; Webb James M.; Costello Milton P.E.; Carrboro (N.C.)
  - Carrboro Community Center Pool, 1980 (Tube 763)
    Topographic site plans, Main Pool Plan, Pool Sections, Wading Pool Plan Sections and Details, Pool Details, Hydraulic Schematic, Filter Room Plan and Sections, Detailed Grading, General Contract Final Agreement, Plan of Road Layout for Paving, Grading at Lake, Format of Temporary Job Sign
    Costello Milton P.E.; Bell Design Group; Webb James M.; Carrboro (N.C.)
  - Carrboro Community Park (Tube 199)
    Bell Design Group; Carrboro (N.C.)
  - Carrboro Community Park (Tube 219)
    Soils analysis, slope analysis, vegetation
  - Carrboro Community Park (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Tube 213)
    Vegetation analysis, soils analysis, slope analysis, master plan, preliminary master plan, offsite features
    Webb James M.; Bell Design Group; Carrboro (N.C.)
  - Carrboro Community Park (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Tube 214)
    Topographic surveys, overall staking, construction detail, detailed staking, pool complex staking
  - Carrboro Community Park (1 of 2), 1980 (Tube 50)
    Webb James M.; Costello Milton P.E.; Bell Design Group; Carrboro (N.C.)
  - Carrboro Community Park (2 of 2), 1980 (Tube 209)
    Detailed grading, overall planting, detailed staking, construction - plant details, alternatives, pool complex grading, overall grading, pool complex planting, landscape plans
    Bell Design Group; Webb James M.; Carrboro (N.C.)
  - Carteret County Parks and Recreation: Beaufort Township to Lewis Thoroughfare, Lewis Thoroughfare to Beaufort Channel Bridge, Beaufort Channel Bridge to Craven Street, Town Creek Park, 1985 (Tube 140)
    Master landscape plans, aerial view of Beaufort Township to Lewis Thoroughfare, Lewis Thoroughfare to Beaufort Channel Bridge, Beaufort Channel Bridge to Craven Street, Town Creek Park
    Bell Design Group; Carteret County (N.C.)
  - Cary Bank of Fuquay (Tube 738)
    Plan of Parking Lot
  - Cary High School, 1962 (Tube 745)
  - Ceruzzi (Mr. and Mrs. Frank) residence, 1964 (Tube 745)
    Plans and Details, Details
  - Chandler (Bob and Sandra) residence, 1978-1986 (Tube 571)
    Master development plan, site plan
    Bell Design Group; Newberry Truman L. Jr.; Garner (N.C.)
  - Chandler (Bob and Sandra) residence, 1978-1987 (Tube 573)
    Site plan, master development plan
  - Chapel Hill: City parking lot (Tube 739)
  - Chapel Hill Fire Station, 1964 (Tube 730)
  - Charles F. Carroll Junior High School, 1963-1968 (Tube 244)
    Site planting plan, court planting, details, court construction
  - Charles F. Carroll Junior High School (Tube 248)
    Sign
  - Chatham Manufacturing Company Land Surveys, 1981-1987 (Tube 522)
    Bell Design Group; Elkin (N.C.)
  - Chatham (Thomas and Anna) residence, 1973 (Tube 859)
    Property Map, Main Level Floor Plan, Lower Level Floor Plan
    Bell Design Group; Linville (N.C.)
  - Chatham (Thomas and Anna) residence, 1977 (Tube 858)
    Topographic Site Plans
    Bell Design Group; Dermid Engineers; Linville (N.C.)
  - Chatham (Thomas L. and Anna H.) residence, 1968-1973 (Tube 585)
    Highway Map, County Map
    Ashe Engineers, Planners, and Surveyors; North Carolina State Highway Commission Planning and Research Department; Alleghany County (N.C.)
  - Chavis Heights: Dwelling unit renovation work, 1976 (Tube 800)
    Bell Design Group; Haskins & Rice, Architects; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Child (Ms. Lee) residence (Tube 93)
    Landscape master plan, axonometric view of scheme 2
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Chapel Hill (N.C.)
  - Child (Ms. Lee) residence (Tube 94)
  - Child (Ms. Lee) residence (Tube 553)
    Landscape Master Plans, Site Plans
  - Child (Ms. Lee) residence (Tube 554)
    Landscape Master Plans, Schematic Plans
  - Child (Ms. Lee) residence (Tube 555)
    Landscape Master Plans, Axonometric Views of Schemes 1 and 2
  - Chowan County - Aerial Photograph (Flatfolder 15)
    Chowan County (N.C.)
  - Church Grounds Park (Tube 695)
    Site Plan of Current Ownership
  - CIBA-GEIGY (Tube 21)
    RS&H of North Carolina, Inc.; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - CIBA-GEIGY: Functional plan for the western alternative of the western urban loop, 1992 (Tube 22)
    RS&H of North Carolina, Inc.; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Wilbur Smith Associates, Inc.; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - CIBA-GEIGY: Site plan (Tube 21)
    Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Cimarron Capital, Inc.: Composite map, 1985 (Tube 245)
  - Cimarron Capital, Inc.: Composite map, topographic survey, 1985 (Tube 281)
  - City of Durham: City Hall (Tube 581)
    Plant list, staking and grading
  - Clark Gardens at Fayetteville Museum of Art, 1980 (Tube 849)
    Bell Design Group; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Clark (Mr. and Mrs. Joe) residence, 1988 (Tube 571)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Roanoke (Va.)
  - Clark (Mr. and Mrs. Joe) residence, 1989-1990 (Tube 573)
    Staking, grading, planting, topographic survey, site plan
  - Clark (Mr. and Mrs. W.G., III) subdivision of property (1 of 2), 1966 (Tube 57)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Edgecombe County (N.C.)
  - Clark (Mr. and Mrs. W.G., III) subdivision of Property (2 of 2), 1966 (Tube 730)
  - Clark (Mr. and Mrs. William G.) residence, 1961 (Tube 14)
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Tarboro (N.C.)
  - Classroom Teachers Development, 1968 (Tube 161)
    Hammocks Beach typical unit plans
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Swansboro (N.C.)
  - Cleveland County Memorial Library: Onnie Baker Memorial, 1972 (Tube 231)
    Planting plan, proposed site development
    Shelby (N.C.)
  - Cloverdale Farm: Miller (Larry and Sue) residence, 1976 (Tube 695)
    Bell Design Group; Halifax County (Va.)
  - Clubhouse, 1969 (Tube 508)
    Enlarged Grading Plan
  - Coan (Mr. and Mrs. J.W.) residence, 1967 (Tube 298)
    Landscape plans
  - Cohen (Mr. and Mrs. Stanley) residence, 1976 (Tube 771)
    Landscape lighting, design development phase, site staking, grading and storm drainage
    Laslett Basil G. F.; Laslett William L.; Bell Design Group; Southern Pines (N.C.)
  - Cohen (Mr. and Mrs. Stanley) residence, 1975-1976 (Tube 774)
    Master development plan, alternate guest parking
  - Cohen (Mr. and Mrs. Stanley) residence and stablehouse: Hayfields, 1976 (Tube 507)
    Master Development Plans
    Bell Design Group; Laslett William L.; Southern Pines (N.C.)
  - Coleman (Mr. and Mrs. W. R.) residence (Tube 738)
    Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Rocky Mount (N.C.)
  - Colfax Ward: Greensboro, N.C. Stake, 1983-1984 (Tube 141)
    Planting plan, details, irrigation plan, staking plan, site development, preliminary plan
    Phillips & Miller, Inc.; Bell Design Group; Colfax (N.C.)
  - Collett (John) residence, 1968 (Tube 732)
    Details, Landscape Development Plan
    Harrell & Clark Architects; Childres-Andrews Surveying Company; Richard C. Bell Associates; Morganton (N.C.)
  - Collins (Mr. and Mrs. J. H.) residence (Tube 739)
    Carr, Harrison, Pruden & DePasquale; Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Collins (Mr. and Mrs. J. H.) residence (Tube 738)
  - Colonial Pines Subdivision (Tube 821)
    Site evaluation
    Bell Design Group; Kinston (N.C.)
  - Colony West Professional Park (Flatfolder 23)
    Photographic Negatives: Elevation and Floor Plans, Site Plan, Logo Plan
    Cimarron Capital, Inc.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Commerce Park for Ridgeway Enterprises, Inc., 1964 (Tube 732)
    Floor Plans, Elevations, Foundation Plans, Site Plans, Master Plan, Electrical Plan, Heating Plan, Structural Plan, Details, Elevations and Wall Sections, Floor Plan Section
  - Conner (Mr. and Mrs. Allen) residence, 1968-1969 (Tube 738)
    Landscape Development Plan, Staking Plan, Details
  - Contempoville: Vandalia Road Housing Project, 1971 (Tube 647)
    Preliminary plat
    Ray Troxell Associates, Inc.; Richard C. Bell Associates; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Contempoville Housing Project for Housing Incorporated, 1971 (Tube 786)
    Site Plans, Plant List and Planting Details, Planting Plans
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Richard C. Bell Associates; William F. Freeman Associates, Architects; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Copeland (Mr. and Mrs. Ronald) residence (Tube 750)
  - Coral Bay Club (1 of 2), 1974 (Tube 128)
    Details, planting plan, site development plan
  - Coral Bay Club (2 of 2), 1974 (Tube 129)
  - Coral Bay Condominium Complex (1 of 2), 1970 (Tube 270)
    Landscape plan, grading, lighting, planting
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Willis James B. Jr.
  - Coral Bay Condominium Complex (2 of 2), 1970 (Tube 278)
  - The Country Inn (Tube 727)
    Landscape Plans and Details
    Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Courtney Square Apartments, 1984 (Tube 787)
    Site Plans, Landscape Improvements, Construction Details
  - "The Cove" Amphitheatre: The Jamestown Corporation, owners, 1957 (Tube 497)
    Side view Elevations, Staking Plans, Architectural Plans, Grading Plan, Planting Plan, Site Details
    Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Williamsburg (Va.)
  - Cowan (Dr. and Mrs. Robert) residence (1 of 2), 1978 (Tube 580)
  - Cowan (Dr. and Mrs. Robert) residence (2 of 2), 1978 (Tube 581)
    Proposed site changes
  - Cowell (Phylis S.) residence, 1983 (Tube 730)
    Landscape Irrigation Plan, Landscape Construction Details, Plans, and Sections, Staking Plan, Landscape Grading Plan, Landscape Planting Plan, Landscape Plan, Site Plan
    Bell Design Group; Rocky Mount (N.C.)
  - Cowell (Phylis S.) residence (Tube 747)
    Floor Plan
  - Cox (Mr. and Mrs. Robert N.) residence, 1982 (Tube 572)
    Planting Plans, Grading Plans, Staking Plans, Sediment and Erosion Control
    Salem (Va.)
  - CP&L Energy: Environmental Center (1 of 2), 1974 (Tube 727)
    Planting Plan, Plant List, Elevations & Details, Site Entrance, Building Front Area, Entrance Terrace Area, Site Plans
    Bell Design Group; McKimmon, Rogers and Associates, Architects; North Carolina
  - CP&L Energy: Environmental Center (2 of 2), 1974 (Tube 304)
    McKimmon, Rogers and Associates, Architects; Bell Design Group
  - Craven County Industrial Center, 1977 (Tube 557)
    Site Plans, General Development Plans, Preliminary Land use Plans, Elevations and Signage
    Rose, Pridgen, & Freeman, Inc; Bell Design Group; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Craven County Technical Institute (Tube 248)
    Master site plan, staking plan, grading plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Peterson John N. AIA; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Craven County Technical Institute, 1969-1971 (Tube 246)
    Staking plan, grading plan, master plan, site plan, enlarged detail plan, site work
  - Craven County Technical Institute, 1968-1971 (Tube 247)
    Staking plan, grading plan, master plan, site plan
  - Creed (Mr. and Mrs. John L., Jr.) residence, 1967 (Tube 739)
    Landscape Planting Plan
    MacMillan & MacMillan Architects; Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Cricket Inn (1 of 2), 1983 (Tube 50)
    Ray Troxell Associates, Inc.; Bell Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Cricket Inn (2 of 2), 1983 (Tube 557)
  - Croatan School (1 of 2), 1986 (Flatfolder 23)
    Photographic Negative: Site Plan
    Willis Architects; Bell Design Group; Carteret County (N.C.)
  - Croatan School (2 of 2), 1986 (Tube 510)
    Site Plans, Master Plans, Grading and Storm Drainage Plan, Key Plan, Drawings
  - Croatan School (1 of 3), 1986-1987 (Tube 795)
    Floor Plans, Detailed Planting Plan, Topographic Plans, Master Plans, Detail Plan
  - Croatan School (2 of 3), 1986-1987 (Tube 798)
    Food Service, Elevations and Sections, Elevations, Media Center, Wall Sections and Details
    Bell Design Group; Willis Architects; Carteret County (N.C.)
  - Croatan School (3 of 3), 1986-1987 (Tube 830)
    Schematic Site Development Plan, Sedimentation and Erosion Control Plan, Construction Details, Courtyard Plans, Detailed Staking, Overall Planting, Overall Staking, Irrigation Plans and Details, Site Plan and Water System, Grading, Site Plans
  - Croatan School, 1987 (Tube 832)
    Site Plan, Floor Plans
  - Cross Creek Savings & Loan, 1968 (Tube 730)
  - Crowell (Mr. and Mrs. Giles) residence, 1965 (Tube 738)
    Preliminary Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Lexington (N.C.)
  - Crystal Oaks Townhomes (Tube 245)
    Brockwell-Hoke Architects, Inc; Durham (N.C.)
  - Crystal Oaks Townhomes (Tube 853)
  - Cumberland County Public Library, 1985 (Tube 258)
    MacMillan & MacMillan Architects; Bell Design Group; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Cumberland County Public Library, 1984-1985 (Tube 262)
    Staking and grading plan, planting plan, landscape development, site plan, roof plan
    Bell Design Group; MacMillan & MacMillan Architects; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Cutter Laboratories, Inc./Cutter-Vitrum, Inc.: Intralipid Project, 1979 (Tube 831)
    Grading and Storm Drainage, Planting, Construction Details, Site Assessment, Lobby Design, Proposed Landscape Development
    Bell Design Group; Clayton Township (N.C.)
  - D & J Pontiac-Olds, Inc., 1968 (Tube 829)
    Grading Study Plan, Master Development Plans, Elevations, Floor Plans
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Louisburg (N.C.)
  - Dalton (Mr. and Mrs. Parks, Jr.) residence, 1979 (Tube 515)
    Construction details, site plan, planting, grading, storm drainage, staking
    Bell Design Group; Charlotte (N.C.)
  - Dalton (Mr. and Mrs. Parks, Jr.) residence (Tube 527)
  - Daniel (Dr. and Mrs. Tom B.) residence, 1958 (Tube 827)
    Site Plans, Elevations, Proposed Front Elevation
    Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Daniels (Frank and Julia) residence, 1986 (Tube 54)
  - Daniels (Frank and Julia) residence, 1987 (Tube 211)
  - Daniels (Frank and Julia) residence (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Tube 270)
    Irrigation, lighting plan, grading, drainage, staking, utilities, wall fountain in rear garden, revised grading plan, residential development plan
  - Daniels (Frank and Julia) residence (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Tube 275)
    Wood fence details, elevations, floor plans, preliminary entrance design
  - Daniels (Frank and Julia) residence (Tube 55)
  - Daniels (Mr. and Mrs. Moncie L., Jr.) residence, 1962 (Tube 829)
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Manteo (N.C.)
  - Danville Community College (Tube 771)
    Master plan, existing topographic plan
    Calvert, Lewis & Smith; Danville (Va.)
  - Danville Community College (Tube 160)
    Calvert, Lewis & Smith; Bell Design Group; Danville (Va.)
  - Danville Public Health Center (1 of 2), 1978 (Tube 516)
    Staking plan, construction details
  - Danville Public Health Center (2 of 2), 1978 (Tube 517)
    Planting plan, grading plan
  - Davenport (Mr. and Mrs. R.E.) residence, 1969-1970 (Tube 827)
    Landscape Plan, Planting Plan, Details, Landscape Improvement Plans, Plan at New Deck Area, Staking Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Farmville (N.C.)
  - Davis (Dr. and Mrs. James H.) residence: Berry Hill Farm (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Property map
  - Davis (Dr. and Mrs. James H.) residence: Berry Hill Farm (Flatfolder 27)
  - Davis (Dr. and Mrs. James H.) residence: Berry Hill Farm (1 of 2), 1976 (Tube 833)
    Photo static Map
  - Davis (Dr. and Mrs. James H.) residence: Berry Hill Farm (2 of 2), 1976 (Tube 714)
    Smith and Smith Surveyors; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Davis (Mr. and Mrs. Phil) residence (Tube 651)
    Floor plans, elevations, wall sections
  - Day (Mr. and Mrs. Richard C.) residence, 1963 (Tube 828)
    Landscape Plan, Planting Plan
  - De la Queriere (Susan and Yves) residence, 1997 (Tube 54)
    Residential addition and site improvements
  - De la Queriere (Susan and Yves) residence, 1996 (Tube 55)
  - De la Queriere (Susan and Yves) residence, 1996-1997 (Tube 210)
    Residential addition
  - De la Queriere/Nasser residence, 1997 (Tube 212)
    Entrance terrace plan
  - Dental Clinic for Westview Building, Inc., 1959 (Tube 507)
    Godwin and Bell, A.S.L.A.; Wilson (N.C.)
  - Department of Natural Resources and Community Development: Outdoors' North Carolina 1982, 1981 (Tube 727)
    Floor Plans
  - Devane (Mr. and Mrs. J.D., III) residence, 1980 (Tube 54)
    Bell Design Group; Sanford (N.C.)
  - Devane (Mr. and Mrs. J.D., III) residence (Tube 515)
    Landscape development concept plan
  - Devane (Mr. and Mrs. J.D., III) residence, 1974-1980 (Tube 518)
    Construction details, foundation plan, floor plans, elevations, sections, details, roof framing, specifications
  - Devane (Mr. and Mrs. J.D., III) residence, 1979 (Tube 527)
    Existing conditions, construction details
  - Development of Block Island (Tube 29)
    Harvard University Graduate School of Design
  - Doctors Building of Chapel Hill, Inc., 1964 (Tube 827)
    Details, Plans for Plant List, Site Plans
  - The Dogwood Gardens, 1963-1964 (Tube 829)
    Main Entrance, Master Plan, Details, Master Planting Plan, Study Detail of Construction
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Bell Richard C. 1928-; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Dougherty Administration area topographical survey, 1990 (Tube 97)
    Burke County (N.C.)
  - Downey (Mr. and Mrs. Charles M. and family) residence, 1973 (Tube 499)
    Site Development Plans, Building Elevations
    White W. P. Dinsmore Architect; Bell Design Group; Linville (N.C.)
  - Downey residence (1 of 2), 1973 (Tube 826)
    Elevations, Revised Elevations Showing Entry Stairs, Revised Site Plan, Overall Site Plan, Site Plan Showing Grading and Detail Indication
  - Downey residence (2 of 2), 1973 (Tube 829)
    Construction Details, Site Plans, Details, Plan of Entry
  - Downtown New Bern (Tube 711)
    Design Plans
  - Downtown New Bern (Tube 834)
    Proposed Street Plan
    New Bern (N.C.)
  - Duke Homesites: Duke University, 1966 (Tube 829)
    Schematic Subdivision Study
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Boney and Newcomb; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University: Married Students' Housing (1 of 2), 1964 (Tube 164)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; J.N. Pease & Company, Inc.; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University: Married Students' Housing (2 of 2), 1964 (Tube 527)
    Staking plan, plant list
  - Duke Univeristy: University President's House (1 of 2), 1966 (Tube 828)
    Preliminary Site Improvements and Landscape Study, Site Plans
    Alden B. Dow Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University: University President's House (2 of 2), 1966 (Tube 718)
    Preliminary Improvements and Landscape Study
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Alden B. Dow Associates; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (1 of 3), 1990 (Tube 168)
    Site plan submittal
    Cooper, Robertson & Partners; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (2 of 3), 1990 (Tube 672)
    Site plan, boundary exhibit, expanded site plan, future development plan, elevations, sections, site elevations, stair/elevator towers
    Walker Parking Consultants; Cooper, Robertson & Partners; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (3 of 3), 1990 (Tube 794)
    Grading, Construction Documents, Sign Schedule and Components, Sign Mounting Details, Site Plantings and Laws, Site Grading/Sediment Control/Drainage
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Walker Parking Consultants; Cooper, Robertson & Partners; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III, 1990-1991 (Tube 171)
    East and west elevations, planting plan, development plan submittal
    Cooper, Robertson & Partners; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III, 1990-1992 (Tube 348)
    Construction details, grading plan, site development plan, site plantings and lawns, site grading, driveway and storm sewer profiles, site staking/utilities
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (1 of 2), 1990-1994 (Tube 416)
    Development plan submittal, Fulton Street landscape improvements
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Walker Parking Consultants; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (2 of 2), 1990-1994 (Tube 673)
    Site plantings and lawns, Fulton Street landscape improvements, staking, grading, planting, details, topographic survey, demolition plan, development plan, site staking, sediment control, driveway and storm sewer profiles, construction details, irrigation plan
    Walker Parking Consultants; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Cooper, Robertson & Partners; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (1 of 6), 1991 (Tube 188)
    Construction details, level plans, elevations
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (2 of 6), 1991 (Tube 189)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (3 of 6), 1991 (Tube 856)
    One through Seven Level Plans, Column Schedule, Beam Schedule, Slab Schedule, West Grade Elevation, East Grade Elevation, Structural Details, Typical Level Plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Cooper, Robertson & Partners; Walker Parking Consultants; Durham (N.C.)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (4 of 6), 1991 (Tube 674)
    Topographic survey, demolition plan, development plan, site staking, site grading, sediment control, drainage, driveway and storm sewer profiles, site plantings and lawns, construction details, irrigation plan
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (5 of 6), 1991 (Tube 675)
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III (6 of 6), 1991 (Tube 797)
    Site Plantings and Lawns, Demolition Plan, Site Staking, Cover Sheet, Site Plans, Drainage Calculations
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III, 1991-1993 (Tube 349)
    Irrigation plan and details, staking, grading, planting and details, site plantings and lawns
  - Duke University Medical Center: Parking Garage III, 1991-1994 (Tube 417)
    Site grading, sediment control, drainage, planting and details, site staking, irrigation plan
  - Dunes of Dare Sacred Gardens - Dunes of Dare Garden Club, 1969 (Tube 829)
    Master Landscape Development Plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Kitty Hawk (N.C.)
  - Durham (Flatfolder 30)
  - Durham Ambulatory Surgical Center, 1984 (Tube 449)
    Site Plans, Site Plan - Phase Two
    O'Brien/Atkins Associates, PA; Durham (N.C.)
  - Durham Coca-Cola Bottling Company, 1961 (Tube 739)